Website README
 Image size: 2000px x 1500px
	5:4 aspect ratio

Go to github.com, click New repository, name it (e.g. portfolio-website), set it to Public, and don't initialize with a README. Then connect and push:


git remote add origin https://github.com/YOUR_USERNAME/portfolio-website.git
git branch -M main
git push -u origin main
Step 3: Enable GitHub Pages

In your GitHub repo → Settings → Pages → under "Branch" select main and / (root) → Save.

GitHub will give you a URL like https://yourusername.github.io/portfolio-website — it'll be live in a minute or two.

Step 4: Connect your custom domain

In the same Pages settings, enter your domain (e.g. www.yourdomain.com) in the Custom domain field and save. GitHub will create a CNAME file in your repo automatically.

Then go to your domain registrar (wherever you bought the domain) and add these DNS records:

CNAME record: www → yourusername.github.io
If you want the apex domain (yourdomain.com without www), add four A records pointing to GitHub's IPs: